Guide to the Deane W. Malott papers, 1951-1964
Malott, Deane W. papers, 1951-1964
- Board of Trustees - Joseph P. Ripley., 1958-59 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Board of Trustees - Francis H. Scheetz. Summerskill, John., 1958-59 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Board of Trustees - Leslie R. Severinghaus., 1958 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Board of Trustees - John P. Syme., 1959 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Board of Trustees - Myron C. Taylor., 1958-59 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  Myron and Anabel Taylor Foundation.
- Board of Trustees - Allan H. Treman. Big Red Barn., 1957-58 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Board of Trustees - Maxwell M. Upson., 1957-59 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Board of Trustees - Frederic C. Wood., 1958 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Board of Trustees - Executive Committee., 1957-59 (Box 23, Folder 20-22)
- Board of Trustees - Investment Committee., 1958-59 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- Cornell University Library Board., 1958-59 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Board of Trustees - Buildings and Properties Committee., 1958-59 (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Board of Physical Education and Athletics., 1957-58 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  Newhall, Herbert F.
- Willard Straight Hall Board of Governors., 1957 (Box 23, Folder 27)
- College of Engineering Council., 1958 (Box 23, Folder 28)
- New York Hospital - Cornell Medical Center School of Nursing., 1958 (Box 23, Folder 29)
- New York State College of Agriculture and the Agricultural Experiment Stations Council., 1959 (Box 23, Folder 30)
- New York State College of Home Economics Council., 1957 (Box 23, Folder 31)
- Graduate School of Business and Public Administration Council., 1957-58 (Box 23, Folder 32)
- Deans and Heads of Departments., 1958 (Box 23, Folder 33)
- Office of Public Information. Potter, John Mason., 1958-59 (Box 23, Folder 34)
- Communism, Faculty., 1954 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  Emanuel, Victor; Singer, Marcus; Steinmetz, Harry C.
- Academic Freedom. Glasser, Abraham., 1958 (Box 23, Folder 36)
- Marcus Singer., 1954-56 (Box 23, Folder 37)
- Marcus Singer. MacDonald, John W.; Reynolds, Herbert B., 1955-57 (Box 23, Folder 38)
- Lloyd H. Elliott., 1956 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  Speech by Assistant to the President.
- President's Report., 1957-58 (Box 23, Folder 40)
- Administrative Staff Meetings., 1957-59 (Box 23, Folder 41-44)
- Notices to Staff., 1958 (Box 23, Folder 45)
- Speeches and Articles by DWM., 1958 (Box 23, Folder 46)
- Inventory., 1953-56 (Box 23, Folder 47)
- J. L. Zwingle., 1959 (Box 23, Folder 48)
- Planning and Development., 1958-59 (Box 23, Folder 49)
- Gifts., 1959 (Box 23, Folder 50)
- Gifts., 1958-59 (Box 23, Folder 51)
- Gifts., 1958 (Box 23, Folder 52)
- Gifts., 1957-58 (Box 23, Folder 53)
- Gifts., 1957 (Box 23, Folder 54)
- Gift Report., 1957-58 (Box 23, Folder 55)
- Cornell University Bequest Program., 1958 (Box 23, Folder 56)
- Cornell University Council., 1959 (Box 23, Folder 57)
- Cornell Regional Meetings., 1959 (Box 23, Folder 58)
- Cornell University Associates., 1957-59 (Box 23, Folder 59)
  Cliggott, Richard T.
- Parents Weekend., 1958 (Box 23, Folder 60)
- Vice President for Research., 1957-59 (Box 23, Folder 61)
  Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory.
- Automotive Crash Injury Research Program., 1958 (Box 23, Folder 62)
- Vice President for Business., 1958-59 (Box 23, Folder 63)
  Burton, John E. Student Demonstration, 1958.
- Vice President for Business., 1957-58 (Box 23, Folder 64)
  Burton, John E. Willard Straight Hall.
- Dept. of Buildings and Properties., 1957-58 (Box 23, Folder 65)
- Housing Research Center., 1958 (Box 23, Folder 66)
  Loberg, Harry J.
- Board on Traffic Control., 1958 (Box 23, Folder 67)
- Residential Halls., 1957-58 (Box 23, Folder 68)
- Purchasing Dept., 1959 (Box 23, Folder 69)
- Vice President for Student Affairs., 1958 (Box 23, Folder 70)
- Council on Student Affairs., 1958-59 (Box 23, Folder 71)
  Summerskill, John. Committee on Reorganization of Student Government; Committee on Student Conduct; Student Committee on Reorganization of Student Conduct and Affairs; Committee on Academic Work and Interest.
- Faculty., 1958-59 (Box 23, Folder 72)
  Feil, J. P.; Morrison, Philip; Hacker, Louis M.; Konvitz, Milton R.; Summerskill, John.
- Students and student Events., 1958 (Box 23, Folder 73)
- Fraternities., 1959 (Box 23, Folder 74-75)
- Dormitories., 1958-59 (Box 23, Folder 76)
- Student Conduct Study., 1958 (Box 23, Folder 77)
  A Report by the Deans of the Undergraduate Schools and Colleges; Vice President for Student Affairs.
- Council on Student Affairs., 1957 (Box 23, Folder 78)
- Council on Student Affairs., 1956 (Box 23, Folder 79)
- Committee on Student Affairs., 1956-57 (Box 23, Folder 80)
  Attrition studies.
- Freshmen Orientation Program., 1958 (Box 23, Folder 81)
- Office of the Treasurer., 1957-59 (Box 23, Folder 82)
  Upson, Maxwell M.; Newman, Floyd R.
- Budget., 1958-59 (Box 23, Folder 83)
- Office of the Director of the Budget., 1957-58 (Box 23, Folder 84)
- Tuition and Fees., n.d. (Box 23, Folder 85)
- Office of the University Counsel., 1958-59 (Box 23, Folder 86)
  Meigs, Robert B.
- Office of the University Counsel., 1957-58 (Box 23, Folder 87)
- Office of Admissions., 1958-59 (Box 23, Folder 88-89)
- Applicants for Admission., 1957-58 (Box 24, Folder 1-3)
- Office of the Registrar., 1957-59 (Box 24, Folder 4-5)
- Registration and Schedules Committee., 1958-59 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Office of the Controller., 1959 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  Peterson, Arthur H.
- Commencement., 1957 (Box 24, Folder 8-9)
- Deans of Men and Women., 1957-59 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  Brooks, Dorothy V. N.; Baldwin, Frank C. Chi Gamma; Student deportment.
- Counselor of Foreign Students., 1957-59 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  Williams, David B.
- University Printer., 1957 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Students., 1957-59 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Fraternities and Interfraternity Council. Fraternities with restrictive clauses., 1957-58 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Orientation Program., 1957 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Student Council., 1958 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  Kellogg, K. Peter.
- Cornell Daily Sun., 1957 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  Sale, J. Kirkpatrick.
- Independent Student Association., 1958 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Sororities., 1956-58 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  Hunt, Nancy; Brooks, Dorothy V. N. Chi Gamma; Sigma Kappa.
- Women' s Self Government Association., 1957 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- WVBR., 1958 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Office of the University Proctor., 1958 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  George, Lowell T. Committee on Public Safety.
- Cornell University Press., 1958 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- Official Publications., 1958 (Box 24, Folder 24)
- Cornell university Library., 1957-58 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  McCarthy, Stephen A. Board; Olin Library.
- Olin Library., 1959 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  Treman, Allan H.; Lee, D. Boardman; Wade, Harry V.; Guerlac, Henry. Boardman Hall.
- Olin Library., 1959 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  Neufeld, Maurice F. Boardman Hall.
- Olin Library., 1958-59 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  Requardt, Gustav J.; Owings, Nathaniel A.; Collyer, John L.; Newman, Floyd R.; Clarke, Gilmore D. Boardman Hall.
- Archives and Regional History., 1957-59 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  Fox, Edith M.; Donlon, Mary H.; Gannett, Frank E.; Ives, Irving M.; Gannett, Caroline Werner.
- Committee on Art in the Research Library., 1957-59 (Box 24, Folder 30)
- Television., 1957-58 (Box 24, Folder 31)
- Festival of Contemporary Arts., 1957-58 (Box 24, Folder 32)
- WHCU., 1957-58 (Box 24, Folder 33)
- Willard Straight Hall., 1958-59 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  Whiting, Edgar A.; Summerskill, John. Noyes Lodge.
- Willard Straight Hall., 1957-58 (Box 24, Folder 35)
- Willard Straight Hall Board of Governors., 1958-59 (Box 24, Folder 36)
- Noyes Lodge., 1958 (Box 24, Folder 37)
- Placement Service., 1958 (Box 24, Folder 38)
- Andrew Dickson White Museum of Art. Marks, A. Lester; Solomon, Alan R., 1958-59 (Box 24, Folder 39)
- Big Red Barn., 1957-58 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  Ryon, S. Russell.
- Financial Aids Office., 1958 (Box 24, Folder 41)
- University Faculty., 1958-59 (Box 24, Folder 42)
- University Faculty., 1957-58 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  Committee on Long Range Planning.
- University Faculty - Minutes., 1957-59 (Box 24, Folder 44-47)
- Dean of the University Faculty., 1957-59 (Box 24, Folder 48)
  Hanson, C. Arnold; Abrams, Meyer H. Committee on Long Range Planning.
- Faculty Committees., 1957-59 (Box 24, Folder 49)
- University Faculty Council., 1957-58 (Box 24, Folder 50)
- Committee on Military Curricula., 1957-58 (Box 24, Folder 51)
- University Lectures., 1957-59 (Box 24, Folder 52)
- Prizes., 1958-59 (Box 24, Folder 53)
- Committee on Student Conduct., 1958 (Box 24, Folder 54)
  Humphreyville, Theresa; Newhall, Herbert F.; Bishop, Morris G.; Collyer, John L.; Summerskill, John. Committee on Student Activities; "Cornell University Social Events Standards"; Student deportment.
- Committee on Student Conduct., 1958-59 (Box 24, Folder 55)
  Snickenberger, Walter A.; Newhall, Herbert F.; Haloua, Gaston D. Committee on Student Activities
- Committee on Student Conduct., 1957-58 (Box 24, Folder 56)
  Sale, J. Kirkpatrick; Farina, Richard; Detweiler, A. Henry; Sale, William (student).
- Student Activities., 1957-59 (Box 24, Folder 57)
  Humphreyville, Theresa. Committee on Student Affairs; Committee on Student Activities; Chi Gamma.
- Student Activities., 1957-58 (Box 24, Folder 58)
  Lee, D. Boardman. Apartment registration policies; Social Events Code; Committee on Student Conduct.
- Student Activities., 1957 (Box 24, Folder 59)
  Committee on Student Conduct.
- Student Activities., 1957 (Box 24, Folder 60)
  Committee on Student Activities.
- Committee on Undergraduate Scholarships., 1957-59 (Box 24, Folder 61)
- Committee on the Scheduling of Public Events., 1958 (Box 24, Folder 62)
- Committee on Calendar., 1957-58 (Box 24, Folder 63)
- Committee on Music., 1958 (Box 24, Folder 64)
- Committee on the Economic Status of the Faculty., 1958-59 (Box 24, Folder 65)
- Committee on the Economic Status of the Faculty., 1957 (Box 24, Folder 66)
- Necrology., 1957-59 (Box 24, Folder 67-68)
- Committee on Academic Freedom and Tenure. Hanson, C. Arnold; Konvitz, Milton R.; Finley, Moses I.; Heimlich, Simon W. Communism; Academic freedom., 1958-59 (Box 24, Folder 69)
- Pensions and Retirement., 1957 (Box 24, Folder 70)
- Salaries of Faculty and Assistants., 1957 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- John L. Senior Professorship., 1958 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  Farr, Newton C.; Rossiter, Clinton L.; Perkins, Dexter.
- John L. Senior Professorship., 1958 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  Rossiter, Clinton L.; Woodward, C. Vann; Perkins, Dexter.
- New York State College of Agriculture., 1959 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  Myers, William I.; Palm, Charles E. Committee on the Education Program of the College; Liberty Hyde Bailey Hortorium.
- New York State College of Agriculture., 1958 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  Myers, William I.; Palm, Charles E.; Adams, Morton; Brady, Nyle C.; King, Joseph P.
- New York State College of Agriculture., 1958 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  Myers, William I.; Palm, Charles E. Candidates for deanship.
- New York State College of Agriculture., 1957-58 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  Myers, William I.; Palm, Charles E.; Boynton, Damon; Bailey, Liberty Hyde.
- New York State College of Agriculture -Departments., 1957-59 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  Mott, Russell C.; Summerskill, John; Kellogg, Peter Paul. Fairleigh Dickinson University.
- Laboratory of Ornithology., 1957-59 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  Alien, Arthur A.
- Extension Services., 1958-59 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  Bond, Maurice C.
- College of Architecture., 1957-59 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  Mackesey, Thomas W.; Clarke, Gilmore D.; Detweiler, A. Henry.
- College of Arts and Sciences., 1957-59 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  Mineka, Francis E.; Blackall, Eric A.; Cushman, Robert E. Society of Fellows in the Humanities (Proposed); Lilly Endowment.
- Departments in the College of Arts and Sciences., 1958 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Dept. of Chemistry., 1958-59 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  American Chemical Society.
- Dept. of Economics., 1957-58 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Dept. of Far Eastern Studies., 1957 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  Kahin, George McT.; Dean, Arthur H.
- Dept. of History., 1957-59 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Division of Modern Languages., 1957-58 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Dept. of Music., 1957-59 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  Scheetz, Francis H.; Austin, William W.; Sokol, Thomas A.
- Band., 1957-58 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Sage Chapel Choir., 1958 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- Dept. of Sociology and Anthropology., 1957 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- College of Engineering., 1958-59 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  Corson, Dale R.; Hollister, Solomon C. Computers.
- College of Engineering., 1957-58 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  Hollister, Solomon C.; Pew, Joseph N.; Winding, C. C. Computers; Carpenter Hall; American Society for Engineering Education.
- College of Engineering., 1958-59 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  Grumann, Leroy R.; Corson, Dale R. College of Engineering Council.
- Sibley School of Mechanical Engineering., 1957 (Box 25, Folder 26)
- School of Electrical Engineering. Malti, Michel G., 1957-59 (Box 25, Folder 27)
- School of Chemical and Metallurgical Engineering., 1957-58 (Box 25, Folder 28)
- New York State College of Home Economics. Canoyer, Helen G.; Humphreyville, Theresa. Admissions., 1958-59 (Box 25, Folder 29)
- New York State College of Home Economics. Canoyer, Helen G.; Humphreyville, Theresa; Failing, Jean; Loberg, Harry J. Housing Research Center. Admissions., 1957-58 (Box 25, Folder 30)
- New York State Veterinary College., 1957-59 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  Poppensiek, George C.; Hagan, William A.; Whitlock, John H. American Veterinary Medical Association.
- Cornell University Medical College., 1958-59 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  Hinsey, Joseph C.; David, Donald K.; Loveless, Mary; Kennedy, Fuzz; Deitrick, John E.; Ward, J. Carlton.
- Cornell University Medical College. Hinsey, Joseph C., 1959 (Box 25, Folder 33)
- Cornell University Medical College. Deitrick, John E. New York Hospital - Cornell Medical Center Foundation., 1958-59 (Box 25, Folder 34)
- Cornell University Medical College., 1957-58 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  Deitrick, John E. New York Hospital - Cornell Medical Center Foundation.
- Cornell University Medical College. Deitrick, John E.; Hinsey, Joseph C., 1957-58 (Box 25, Folder 36)
- New York Hospital - Cornell Medical Center Joint Administrative Board., 1957-59 (Box 25, Folder 37)
- Cornell University Medical College -Executive Faculty., 1958-59 (Box 25, Folder 38)
- Sloan-Kettering Institute for Cancer Research., 1958-59 (Box 25, Folder 39)
- Cornell University Medical College Automotive Crash Injury Research Program., 1957-58 (Box 25, Folder 40)
- New York Hospital - Cornell Medical Center Foundation - Titzell Bequest., 1957-58 (Box 25, Folder 41)
  Titzell, Anne Parrish.
- New York Hospital - Cornell Medical Center School of Nursing., 1958 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  Carbery, Muriel R.; Lambertsen, Eleanor C.; Hinsey, Joseph C.
- New York Hospital - Cornell Medical Center School of Nursing., 1957-58 (Box 25, Folder 43)
- Law School., 1957-59 (Box 25, Folder 44)
  Freeman, Harrop A.; Thoron, Gray; Hervey, John G.; Dean, William Tucker. American Bar Association.
- New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations., 1957-59 (Box 25, Folder 45)
  Konvitz, Milton R.; Ross, Arthur M.; Catherwood, Martin P.; Risley, Robert F. Liberian Codification Project; International Cooperation Administration.
- Graduate School of Business and Public Administration., 1958 (Box 25, Folder 46)
  Gibson, Edwin T. Alfred P. Sloan Foundation.
- Graduate School of Business and Public Administration. Sheppard, Charles Stewart; Catchings, Waddill. Whitehall Foundation; Sloan Institute of Hospital Administration., 1957-58 (Box 25, Folder 47)
- Graduate School of Business and Public Administration., 1957-58 (Box 25, Folder 48)
  Sheppard, Charles Stewart; Catchings, Waddill; de Chazeau, Melvin G.
- School of Hotel Administration., 1957-59 (Box 25, Folder 49)
  Meek, Howard B. Statler Foundation.
- School of Education., 1959 (Box 25, Folder 50)
  Stutz, Frederick H.
- School of Education., 1958 (Box 25, Folder 51-52)
- School of Education., 1957 (Box 25, Folder 53)
- Graduate School of Nutrition., 1957-59 (Box 25, Folder 54)
  Barnes, Richard H. ? DeGraff, Herrell F.
- Graduate School., 1957-59 (Box 25, Folder 55)
  McConnell, John W.
- Fellowships., 1957-59 (Box 25, Folder 56)
  IBM; du Pont de Nemours & Co.; General Foods Fund; Standard Oil Company.
- Division of Unclassified Students., 1957-58 (Box 25, Folder 57)
- Air ROTC., 1957-59 (Box 25, Folder 58)
  Dept. of Air Science.
- ROTC., 1957-59 (Box 25, Folder 59)
- Dept. of Physical Education and Athletics., 1957-59 (Box 25, Folder 60)
  Kane, Robert J.; Summerskill, John; Mitchell, Albert K. Student demonstration, 1958.
- Women's Sports., 1957-58 (Box 25, Folder 61)
- Ivy League., 1957-59 (Box 25, Folder 62)
  Harnwell, Gaylord P.
- Ivy League., 1957-58 (Box 25, Folder 63)
  Goheen, Robert F.
- Naval ROTC., 1957-59 (Box 25, Folder 64-65)
- ROTC., 1958-59 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Newman Laboratory of Nuclear Studies., 1957-58 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  Wilson, Robert R.; Newman, Floyd R.
- Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory., 1957-59 (Box 26, Folder 3-8)
- Social Science Research Center., 1957-59 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  Whyte, William F. Program of Latin American Studies (Proposed).
- Summer Session., 1957-59 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Cornell Plantations., 1957-58 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Infirmary and Clinic., 1957-58 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Gannett Clinic., 1957 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  Gannett, Caroline Werner.
- Cornell United Religious Work., 1958 (Box 26, Folder 14-18)
  Jaquith, L. Paul.
- Cornell United Religious Work., 1957-58 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  Olds, Glenn A.; Taylor, Myron C. Sage Chapel.
- Cornell United Religious Work. Olds, Glenn A. CURW Council., 1957 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- Danforth Foundation., 1957-59 (Box 26, Folder 21)
- Danforth Foundation., 1957 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  Brunner, Heinrich Emil.
- Cornell Alumni Fund., 1957-58 (Box 26, Folder 23)
- Alumni Office., 1957-59 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  Bradley, Hunt; Wade, Harry V.; Syme, John P.
- Alumni Trips., 1959 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Alumni Trips., 1958 (Box 26, Folder 26)
- Cornell Clubs., 1959 (Box 26, Folder 27)
- Cornell Clubs., 1958-59 (Box 26, Folder 28)
- Cornell Clubs., 1957-58 (Box 26, Folder 29)
- Cornell Alumni News., 1957-58 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  Cornell Alumni Association of New York City.
- Scholarships and Grants., 1958-59 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  Saperstone, David A. Summerfield Foundation; Chemstrand Corporation; Standard Oil Company; Ford Foundation.
- Scholarships and Grants., 1958 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  Saperstone, David A. National Science Foundation; Esso Education Foundation; Rockefeller Foundation; National Carbon Company; Kaiser Aluminum and Chemical Corporation; Texas Company.
- Scholarships and Grants., 1957-58 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  National Science Foundation; du Pont de Nemours & Co.; Shell Companies Foundation; General Foods Fund; Fund for Adult Education.
- Scholarships and Grants., 1957 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  Union Carbide Corporation; Standard Oil Company; Alcoa Foundation; Crusade Scholarships of the Methodist Church; Eastman Kodak Company.
- Scholarships and Grants., 1957 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  United States Rubber Company; du Pont de Nemours & Co.; Alfred P. Sloan Foundation.
- Cornell National Scholarships., 1958 (Box 26, Folder 36)
- President's Tuition Scholarships., 1958-59 (Box 26, Folder 37)
- Procedures and Policies for Awarding of Scholarships., n.d. (Box 26, Folder 38)
- Rhodes Scholarships., 1958 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  French, W. H.
- Prizes., 1955-58 (Box 26, Folder 40)
- Messenger Lectures., 1957-59 (Box 26, Folder 41)
  Pauling, Linus; Hoyle, Fred; Wigglesworth, V. B.; Burns, Arthur F.; Tillich, Paul.
- Extramural Courses., 1957 (Box 26, Folder 42)
- Fund for Adult Education., 1958 (Box 26, Folder 43)
- Veterinary Virus Research Institute., 1957 (Box 26, Folder 44)
- State University of New York., 1958 (Box 26, Folder 45)
  Moore, Frank C.; Palm, Charles E.; Carlson, William S. Board of Trustees; Blegen Report re a centralized State University of New York.
- State University of New York., 1957-58 (Box 26, Folder 46)
- State University of New York., 1957 (Box 26, Folder 47)
  Centralized State University of New York; New York State Graduate School of Education at Cornell (Proposed).
- New York State Education Dept., 1957-58 (Box 26, Folder 48)
  Kille, Frank R.; Nyquist, Ewald B.; Personius, Catherine J. New York State College of Home Economics; Inter-institutional cooperation.
- New York State Education Dept., 1957 (Box 26, Folder 49)
  True, Virginia. Inter-institutional cooperation.
- New York State Education Dept., 1957 (Box 26, Folder 50)
  Alien, James E. New York State Graduate School of Education at Cornell (Proposed).
- New York State Education Dept., 1957 (Box 26, Folder 51)
- New York State Education Dept., 1957-59 (Box 26, Folder 52)
  Smith, Esther C.; Alien, James E.; Kille, Frank R.; Fretwell, Elbert K.
- New York State Education Dept., 1958-59 (Box 26, Folder 53)
  Alien, James E. University of the State of New York.
- New York State Committee on Graduate Education., 1958-59 (Box 26, Folder 54)
- Degrees., 1957-59 (Box 26, Folder 55)
- Board of Regents., 1957 (Box 26, Folder 56-58)
  Morse, Frederick A.
- A Miscellaneous., 1960 (Box 26, Folder 59)
  Stern, Leslie W. Committee on the Honor System; Committee on Academic Honor; United States Advanced Research Projects Agency.
- A Miscellaneous., 1960 (Box 26, Folder 60)
  Allport, Hamilton. Alcoa Foundation; Association of Universities of the British Commonwealth.
- American Association of Land-Grant Colleges and State Universities., 1959-60 (Box 26, Folder 61)
- American Association of Land-Grant Colleges and State Universities., 1961 (Box 26, Folder 62-65)
  Alien, Herman R.; Perkins, John A. Centennial Celebration.
- American Association of Land-Grant Colleges and State Universities., 1960-61 (Box 26, Folder 66)
  Richter, Jay; Gibson, Anson W.; Harvill, Richard A.
- American Association of Land-Grant Colleges and State Universities., 1960 (Box 26, Folder 67)
  Patillo, Manning M.; Thackrey, Russell I.; Richter, Jay. Centennial Celebration.
- American Association of Land-Grant Colleges and State Universities., 1960 (Box 26, Folder 68)
  Reference Report.
- American Association of Land-Grant Colleges and State Universities., 1960 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  Richter, Jay; Harvill, Richard A.
- American Association of Land-Grant Colleges and State Universities., n.d. (Box 27, Folder 2)
- American Association of Land-Grant Colleges and State Universities Centennial Celebration., 1959-60 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- American Association of Land-Grant Colleges and State Universities., 1959-60 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  Henry, David D.; Thackrey, Russell I.; Richter, Jay; Gibson, Anson W.
- American Association of Land-Grant Colleges and State Universities., 1959-60 (Box 27, Folder 5-6)
- American Miscellaneous., 1959-61 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  American Association for the Advancement of Science; American Can Company.
- American Council on Education., 1961 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- American Council on Education., 1960 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- American Council on Education., 1959 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  Howes, Raymond F.; Adams, Arthur S.
- Association of American Universities. Hatcher, Harlan., 1960-61 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Association of American Universities., 1960-61 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  Hancher, Virgil M.; Siciliano, Rocco C. Communism.
- Association of American Universities., 1960 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  Hancher, Virgil M.
- Association of American Universities., 1958-60 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  Morrill, J. L.; Branscomb, Harvie.
- Association of Colleges and Universities of the State of New York., 1960 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  McEwen, Robert W.
- Association of Colleges and Universities of the State of New York, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- B Miscellaneous., 1959-60 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  Bache, Harold L.; Bard, F. N. Bethlehem Steel Company.